findery.com 2019-03-18

# Our Privacy Policy • Findery

_Last updated: September 16, 2014 (Information related to the Android app and its features added.)_

We at Findery take your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Policy (a few portions have been adapted from a policy originally provided by [Automattic](http://automattic.com/) ([WordPress.com](http://wordpress.com/))) describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and participate within the Findery community. We also describe various Findery features so you can be mindful of what and where you share content. It is made available under the [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) license. Please read this notice very carefully.

Findery members must be at least 13 years old. If you become aware that your child has created an account, please email us at [privacy@findery.com](mailto:privacy@findery.com).

## What personal information do we collect?

### Information that you elect to share with us

When you create an account, we require an email address (we may send you an email to verify) and username. You may also elect to add a personal picture that represents you within the site and add your real name. Some of this information will be visible to the public, but your email address will remain private. You may modify any of your information at any time via your settings page.

### Information collected automatically

  * When you visit findery.com, and click on the homing button, you will be prompted for permission to use your current location. We do not store this information. If you decline, you'll still have access to every Findery feature.
  * When you access Findery via the mobile web, you will be prompted for permission to use your current location determined via GPS and/or nearby networks and/or cell towers. We do not store this information. If you decline, you'll still have access to every Findery feature.
  * When you access Findery via the iPhone or Android app, you will be asked for permission to use Location Services which enables the app to determine your current physical location via GPS and/or nearby networks and/or cell towers. We do not store this information. If you decline, you won't have access to "Notes Near You" in "Discover" or be able to "Bump" into notes.
  * We gather anonymized user actions for analytics to make Findery better for everyone.

## Creating notes

The key functionality of Findery is leaving stories, information and/or images for your friends or the public to find. As you create these notes you should be mindful of your privacy. You may not want to leave a note publicly that identifies where you live. Additionally, you should be mindful of the privacy of others when you create notes. While you may be comfortable sharing an anecdote of that great party you went to where that crazy lady fell down drunk, your hosts may prefer that their humble abode not be featured in such a way. If you do find that your home has been featured in a way that identifies you as the resident, please contact us at [privacy@findery.com](mailto:privacy@findery.com).

## Finding notes

We've implemented a 10 minute delay related to the notifications around finding a note so that you can "Unfind" a note. If you would like to not associate yourself with a note, follow the directions below to "Unfind."

  * On the web, mouse over your profile picture and then click on the "x".
  * On mobile web, tap on your profile picture and then tap the "x".
  * On the iPhone app, tap on the more options button ("...") and tap "Unfind".
  * On the Android app, the location of this functionality varies depending on device, but try the more options button on the left-hand side of your homing button. Tap "Unfind".  

There's more info in our FAQs.

## How your information is shared

Other than to its employees and contractors who may view your account information as part of their day-to-day efforts, Findery will disclose potentially-personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law.

## How your information is stored

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers. 

## "Bumping" Into Notes (iPhone & Android only)

There is specific feature on the iPhone and Android apps that allows you to be notified of notes by members you follow near your current location. This feature is off by default. If you enable Push Notifications this feature will be enabled, and when your iPhone or Android device travels from one location to another, it will send a request to our server for notes by people you follow within range of a specific geo-location. If such notes are found, a push notification is sent to your phone via the Apple Push Notification Service (iPhone) or Google Cloud Messaging (Android). We only store this information for as long as it takes to process the notification. (Bumping is not included on Android for Nokia X.)

## How we communicate with you

We have a myriad of notifications to keep you in the loop regarding how members are interacting with you and your notes. You can opt-out of some or all of these on your settings page. From time to time, we may send you helpful marketing and non-marketing company notifications. Our marketing messages will contain an unsubscribe link if you'd like to remove yourself from receiving those messages. You won't be able to opt-out of company notifications, but they will be infrequent and directly related to your use of Findery.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Findery uses cookies to help Findery identify and track visitors, their usage of the Findery website, and their website access preferences. Findery visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Findery's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Findery's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## HTML5 Local Storage

HTML5 local storage is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Findery uses local storage to authenticate users to the website and remember recent state, such as the last location of the map. HTML5 Local Storage is required for Findery to work.

## Links to 3rd party sites

Members may include links to 3rd party sites within the notes that they share. Our privacy policy covers only the content on Findery. Please take care when visiting any third party sites.

## Business Transfers

If Findery or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the event that Findery goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Findery may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. That said, we will communicate this transfer to you in a timely manner prior to the event so that you may determine whether or not you'd like to continue using Findery.

## Ads

Advertising may appear within Findery. Advertisers will not have any access to member account information beyond what you've specified in your account settings.

## How can I delete my account?

You may terminate your Findery account at any time. There's a link at the bottom of your Settings page on the website that leads to Delete my account. Please note that account deletion is permanent. All of your content will be removed from Findery and your username will be made immediately made available for someone else to register.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and at our sole discretion. If we do then we'll notify you by posting the amended policy on the website or by emailing you of the nature of the modifications along with a link to the modified document so that you can review it. In all cases, use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

Should you have any questions about this document, please contact us at [privacy@findery.com](mailto:privacy@findery.com).

2bkco Inc.  
292 Ivy Street, #B  
San Francisco, CA 94102

## Previous changes to this Privacy Policy

July 29, 2013: Information about private "Home" and "Work" places has been removed as this feature is no longer available.
